How you use machine learning at home or in
私底下或在学习中使用机器学习的方式
school may differ to how it's used within the workplace.
可能与在工作场所的使用方式不一样
Maybe you've participated in
也许为了提升机器学习实践技能
a Kaggle model competition to practice your machine learned skills,
你参加了 Kaggle 模型竞赛
or maybe you've used machine learning
或者你使用了机器学习算法
algorithms to determine the best model for your academic research.
判断在你的学术研究中最合适的模型
For these examples, only complete
对于这些情形来说
the first two components of the machine learning workflow.
你仅仅会完成机器学习流程的前两个环节
Specifically, the end wants
最终只是获得
the most ideal models determined based on performance measures.
根据性能指标确定的最理想模型
This differs from workplace usage because deployment is
这与工作场所的使用方法不一样
typically a critical part of machine learning in the workplace.
因为部署通常是工作场所机器学习的关键环节
Now, there are cases where deployment is included in personal and academic usage.
个人和学术使用情形也会出现部署环节
For example, an academic research group has developed a model that
例如 某个学术研究小组开发了一个模型
predicts the locations risk of mosquito-borne illness with high accuracy rates.
该模型能够预测蚊虫传播疾病的风险地点
Because of the high accuracy rates,
因为准确率很高
these researchers received additional funding to build and
所以这些研究者获得了额外的资金
maintain a web application that deploys their model.
能够构建和维护一个部署该模型的网络应用
In this way, deployment of this web application can be used by
这样的话 医疗人士和政府官员
health and government officials to prevent mosquito-borne illness epidemics.
可以使用该网络应用预防蚊虫传播流行病
For an example of personal usage deployment,
举一个个人用途的部署例子
you decide to create a smartphone application.
你决定创建一款智能手机应用
Imagine you're creating a Magic 8-ball application that provides the user with yes,
假设你创建了一个魔法球应用
no or ask again answers to questions they ask the application.
该应用会针对用户的提问回答“是”、“否”和“再问一遍”
Suppose you design this application,
假设该应用
so instead of providing a random answer,
不会提供随机答案
the application asks the user a series of questions to
而是向用户提出一系列问题
determine the user's mood using sentiment analysis.
并通过情感分析判断用户的情绪
Based upon their mood,
然后根据他们的情绪
your application provides the user with an answer to their question.
向用户提供问题的答案
In the workplace, it's quite common to use deployment with the machine learning workflow.
在工作场所 我们经常在机器学习流程中使用部署环节
Machine learning models are used within an organization's web or
机器学习模型可以用在企业的网络或软件应用中
software applications per activities like fraud detection,
用于检测欺诈性活动
recommender systems, risk assessment, or facial recognition.
构建推荐系统 评估风险或人脸识别
Each of these activities require new inputs to make
每种应用都需要部署的模型
a prediction based upon the deployed model.
根据新的输入做出预测
The organization want to monitor and update
企业希望监控和更新部署的模型
their deployed model to make sure it provides the best predictions over time.
从而一直提供最佳预测
Now that we've learned how machine learning can differ when it's used in the workplace,
我们已经了解了机器学习在工作场所的不同之处
we'll focus on deployment for the rest of this lesson.
下面我们将重点讲解部署环节